bizarreadultclub.com 2004-06-06

# PRIVACY POLICY

Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect:  

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on RB communication Ltd. website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name;   
Address;  
Email address;  
Phone number;

The Way We Use Information: 

We require information about your address etc. ONLY so that we can verify who you are and avoid fraud. Your details will never be used for any other purpose. You are not even added to our e-mail list by joining the site. 

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information: 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by our scripts. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

How To Contact Us: 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +357 25 760075 or send us an email at **customer support**.
